<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>The 10-Min Book Club</title>
    <description>Fast-paced world? No time to read? Struggling to keep up with that ever-growing book list? You're not alone. Get the best insights from bestselling books — all in under 10 minutes. Transform how you think, work, and live with bite-sized episodes that deliver maximum impact.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <link>https://10minbookclub.com/</link>
    <copyright>&#169; 2025 The 10-Min Book Club</copyright>
    <managingEditor>ylijun93@outlook.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>ylijun93@outlook.com</webMaster>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Manual RSS Feed</generator>
    
    <!-- iTunes-specific tags -->
    <itunes:author>Reggie Yang</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Fast-paced world? No time to read? Struggling to keep up with that ever-growing book list? You're not alone. Get the best insights from bestselling books — all in under 10 minutes. Transform how you think, work, and live with bite-sized episodes that deliver maximum impact.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Reggie Yang</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>ylijun93@outlook.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/podcast_image.png"/>
    <itunes:category text="Arts">
      <itunes:category text="Books"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Sample Episode 1 -->
    <item>
      <title>Book 1: The Surrender Experiment: My Journey into Life's Perfection</title>
      <description>What happens when you stop fighting life and start flowing with it? Michael Singer's incredible true story reveals how surrendering to life's natural current led him from a solitary meditator to building a billion-dollar software empire. Discover the counterintuitive secret that transformed his entire existence: saying yes to whatever life presents, even when it terrifies you.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-001</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1l4oB3snXcmeedcoXQ-gOs_TJFble5gCx"
        length="12800000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>9:07</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Discover Michael Singer's incredible journey of surrendering to life's flow and how saying yes to everything led to extraordinary success.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 2: Extreme Ownership – How Navy SEALs Lead and Win</title>
      <description>Diving into Jocko Willink and Leif Babin's powerful leadership principles forged in combat. We explore how taking complete responsibility for everything in your world leads to better outcomes in business, teams, and life.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-002</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1hq9r15fbTbl5PQi6RbMthrn_VP4xPzZo" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>8:58</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Diving into Jocko Willink and Leif Babin's powerful leadership principles about taking complete responsibility.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 3: The Psychology of Money – Timeless Lessons on Wealth, Greed, and Happiness</title>
      <description>Unpacking Morgan Housel's insights into how psychology, emotions, and behavior drive financial decisions. We discuss why being reasonable beats being rational, the power of compounding, and how to build lasting wealth through better money habits.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-003</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1-k_MoaDhyvT1vQmPOaShFsmB-_IopJ10" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>9:30</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Unpacking Morgan Housel's insights into how psychology and behavior drive financial decisions.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 4: Simply Said – Communicating Better at Work and Beyond</title>
      <description>Exploring Jay Sullivan's practical guide to clear, confident communication in professional and personal settings. We cover how to structure your thoughts, engage your audience, and deliver messages that resonate and inspire action.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-004</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=17vYW3M20BW211Qy6udR_hcDu2mYobzPO" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>10:30</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Exploring Jay Sullivan's practical guide to clear, confident communication in professional settings.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 5: Zero to One: Notes on Startups, or How to Build the Future</title>
      <description>Diving into Peter Thiel's contrarian insights on innovation and building monopolistic businesses. We explore how to go from zero to one by creating something entirely new, the importance of secrets, and why competition can be destructive for businesses.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-005</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1SxjrpFwd8VkKDXH6jONMBVi8IHeYMAQk" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>11:51</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Diving into Peter Thiel's contrarian insights on innovation and building monopolistic businesses.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 6: The Let Them Theory: A Life-Changing Tool That Millions of People Can't Stop Talking About</title>
      <description>Discover Mel Robbins' revolutionary approach to finding peace and freedom by simply letting people be themselves. This #1 New York Times, Sunday Times, Amazon, and Audible Bestseller reveals how this simple yet profound mindset shift can end relationship conflicts, reduce stress, and help you reclaim your energy by focusing on what you can actually control.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-006</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1W_4iC9DWOBzV7_sl4qRUErDWvW_WWT97" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>11:51</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Discover Mel Robbins' revolutionary approach to finding peace by letting people be themselves and focusing on what you can control.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 7: How to Win Friends and Influence People</title>
      <description>Unlocking Dale Carnegie's timeless secrets to building powerful relationships and becoming genuinely influential. We dive into the psychology of human connection, exploring how to make people feel important, handle criticism gracefully, and turn opponents into allies through authentic interest and appreciation.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-007</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Buv5cUy4H1rhK439CaS9KPZKst1T15gC" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>8:24</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Unlocking Dale Carnegie's timeless secrets to building powerful relationships and becoming genuinely influential through authentic connection.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 8: Atomic Habits: An Easy and Proven Way to Build Good Habits and Break Bad Ones</title>
      <description>Master the life-changing power of tiny changes with James Clear's groundbreaking system for habit formation. Discover how 1% improvements compound into remarkable results, learn the four-step habit loop that rewires your brain, and unlock the secrets to making good habits inevitable and bad habits impossible. Transform your identity and achieve extraordinary outcomes through the science of small wins.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-008</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1_u3iXnnYIVpjv8Rvt7iAPs-C9saepl9r" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>11:26</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Master the life-changing power of tiny changes with James Clear's system for building habits that stick and breaking the ones that don't.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 9: $100M Offers: How To Make Offers So Good People Feel Stupid Saying No</title>
      <description>Unlock Alex Hormozi's battle-tested formula for creating irresistible business offers that practically sell themselves. Discover the exact framework that transformed struggling businesses into $100M+ enterprises by making prospects feel like idiots for saying no. Learn how to craft offers so compelling that price becomes irrelevant and customers thank you for taking their money.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-009</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1A46jsGCGchIvlbwm1tHx_O71uau54bux" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>10:34</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Unlock Alex Hormozi's battle-tested formula for creating irresistible offers that transform struggling businesses into $100M+ enterprises.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Book 10: Emotional Intelligence 2.0: A Simple Framework for Mastering the Emotions That Control Your Life</title>
      <description>Why do some people effortlessly navigate conflicts while others crumble under pressure? Discover Travis Bradberry and Jean Greaves' groundbreaking system that reveals the four core skills separating high performers from everyone else. Learn how to read emotions like a superpower, manage your reactions under stress, and influence others without manipulation. This isn't about suppressing feelings—it's about leveraging them for unstoppable success in work and life.</description>
      <link>https://reggieyang1126.github.io/my_podcast/feeds/book_club/</link>
      <guid>bookclub-episode-010</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure 
        url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1RkJ6xLBoEJpXbYILwAPnIJKjBnCVDE0t" 
        length="11200000" 
        type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:duration>11:19</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:summary>Discover the four core emotional intelligence skills that separate high performers from everyone else and learn to leverage emotions for success.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>